Guide to the Office of Institutional Advancement Records RG 7
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Office of Institutional Advancement Records
1919-2005
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. Office of Institutional Advancement.
RG 7
16 Linear Feet, 22 boxes
The Office of Institutional Advancement encompasses the Office of Alumni Affairs and the University Relations, which includes the Office of Public Relations and University Publications and Design. This office conducts fund raising and scholarship distribution and creates and disseminates a unified image for the university.
Provenance
Tranferred to the Archives in 2004.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Office of Institutional Advancement at WestConn expands alumni relations and programs, conducts fund raising and scholarship distribution, and creates and disseminates a unified image for the university. This office encompasses Alumni Relations; Development; and University Relations, which includes Public Relations and University Publications and Design.
The Office of Public Relations was responsible for the creation and distribution of information about the university, its faculty, staff, and students until the establishment of the current University Relations Office, which was created in 2005 by merging the Office of Public Relations and University Publications & Design. University Relations create and distribute a number of publications such as Communique and WestConntributors which are filed separately. The Office of Public Relations promoted Western Connecticut State University and the activities of the university to the public in order to bring attention to the university. They also tracked coverage, positive and negative, that the university received in the media.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Office of Alumni Relations includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, financial reports clippings, events announcements, Alumni Directory, and alumni publications.
The class of 1911 Reunion Scrapbook contains photographs of alumnae and their families with very brief information concerning what students have done during the intervening years.
Series 1: Office of Alumni Affairs, 1919-2004 (w/gaps), Box 1 and 2 oversized, Arranged in alphabetical order. Contains: Newsletters, minutes, clippings, financial reports and ledgers, alumnae directory, and scrapbooks.
Series 2: Office of Public Relations, 1941-2001 (w/gaps), Contains: Calendars, clippings, correspondence, publicity and news summaries. Material was assembled from disparate parts and is arranged in the folling manner: materials originally accessioned with the Institutional advancement records is found in box 3. Materials that were previously unaccessioned but processed as the "Office Pulic Relations Records" are contained in boxes 4-6. These records contain include weekly/staff bulletins from 1948-1993. Boxes 7-9 include a 2009 accretion from materials transfered from the basement of Old Main. These materials are made up mainly of press releases from 1989-1996.
The clippings include newspaper articles that regarding events, activities, news, and other important information that was related to the university. Most of the articles come from the News-Times, but there are articles from Western's student newspaper, the Echo. Articles from newspapers such as the Newtown Bee, New York Times, and the Hartford Courant are also a part of this collection.
Although there are some gaps, this series contains articles about the university starting from 1977. The series also includes folders regarding the ground breaking of the Westside classroom building and Ella Grasso Hall. There are also two folders about former Western president Stephen Feldman, including one about his farewell luncheon in 1992.
Series 3: University Relations, 2005-
Series 4: Office of Institutional Advancement, 2003-, Arranged in chronological order. Contains: Correspondence.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically or chronologically within each series.
The files are grouped into 4 series:
Missing Title
Office of Alumni Affairs, 1919-2004 (w/gaps)
Office of Public Relations, 1941-2001 (w/gaps)
University Relations, 2005-
Office of Institutional Advancement, 2003-
Related Material
WCSU Office of Publications and Design.
University and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae -- Connecticut.; Publications.; Press releases.; Danbury (Conn.); Correspondence.; Class reunions -- Connecticut.; Western Connecticut State University. Office of Public Relations .; Western Connecticut State University. Office of University Publications & Design.; Western Connecticut State University. University Relations.; Danbury State College. Office of Alumni Affairs.; Western Connecticut State College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Western Connecticut State University. Office of Alumni Affairs.
- Series I. Office of Alumni Affairs
  General note
  Renamed in Sep 2011 from 1.(RG 7.1) Office of Alumni Affairs
  Alumni Association Presidents since its founding
  Missing Title
  1919/1920 unknown - perhaps no president but the association was founded in 1919
  1920/1921 Annetta Monroe
  1921/1922 Mary Urmston
  1922/1923 Gertrude Murphy
  1923/1924 unknown
  1924/1925 Ann or Anna Hefferan
  1925/1926 Anna Meany or Meaney
  1926/1927 Gladys Stannard
  1927/1928 Harriett Clark
  1928/1929 Josephine Lynch
  1929/1930 Julia Shields Henebry
  1930/1931 Mae Sherwood
  1931/1932 K. Augusta Sutton
  1932/1933 Margaret Lynch
  1933/1934 Julie Fleming
  1934/1935 Marie Coleman Lanigan
  1935/1936 Marie Coleman Lanigan
  1936/1937 Christine Klinzing
  1937/1938 Ruth Dunhman Meder
  1938/1939 Ruth Fischer
  1939/1940 Grace Treat
  1940/1941 Harriet Mabie Leary
  1941/1942 Mrs. Weldon J. Durkin (Barbara Zimmerman)
  1942/1943 May (Mae) Curtin
  1943/1944 May (Mae) Curtin
  1944/1945 May (Mae) Curtin -Note in the 1945 newsletter that Jane Reardon (Secretary) and May Greene (Treasurer) were the the only members of the executive committee and the other members had "resigned due to pressure of other duties." We found other materials that allude to May Curtin as president.
  1945/1946 May (Mae) Curtin
  1946/1947 Helen Vaitkins Selelonis
  1947/1948 Helen Vaitkins Selelonis
  1948/1949 Milton A. Haitsch
  1949/1950 Milton A. Haitsch
  1950/1951 Donald H. Gilbert
  1951/1952 Edward F. McGivern
  1952/1953 Edward F. McGivern
  1953/1954 Edward F. McGivern
  1954/1955 Viola Schultz
  1955/1956 Viola Schultz
  1956/1957 John McCarthy
  1957/1958 John McCarthy
  1958/1959 Harriet Londa Papish
  1959/1960 Harriet Londa Papish
  1960/1961 William McKee
  1961/1962 Annette Fournier
  1962/1963 Ernest Lehman
  1963 Walter Thompson
  1963/1964 Isabelle Farrington
  1964/1965 Robert Simonelli
  1965/1966 Marilyn Tully Boden
  1966/1967 Patrick Cahill
  1967/1968 John Zamary
  1968/1969 Joanna Meyers Baldauf
  1969/1970 Nicholas D. Dagnone
  1970/1971 John Quinlan
  1971/1972 Jack Quinlan
  1972/1973 Terry L. Beninson
  1973/1974 Terry L. Beninson
  1974/1975 Terry L. Beninson
  1975/1976 Eric Wellman
  1976/1977 Eric Wellman
  1977/1978 Eric Wellman
  1978/1979 Sharon Fusco
  1979/1980 Sharon Fusco?
  1980/1981 Robert Bantz
  1981/1982 Elizabeth Wilson
  1982/1983 Alan Skiparis
  1983/1984 Alan Skiparis
  1984/1985 Alan Skiparis
  1985/1986 Alan Skiparis
  1986/1987 Alan Skiparis
  1987/1988 Raymond Lubus
  1988/1989 Alan Skiparis
  1989/1990 Alan Skiparis
  1990/1991 Daryle Dennis
  1991/1992 Daryle Dennis
  1992/1993 Austin C. Drukker, Jr.
  1993/1994 Joan Harrison
  1994/1995 Joan Harrison
  1995/1996 Joan Harrison
  1996/1997 Gail (Hill) Williams
  1997/1998 D. Susanne Snearly
  1998/1999 Christopher A. Shankle
  1999/2000 Christopher A. Shankle
  2000/2001 Kay Schreiber
  2001/2002 Kay Schreiber
  2002/2003 F. Gordon Hallas
  2003/2004 F. Gordon Hallas
  2004/2005 Tom Crucitti
  2005/2006 Tom Crucitti
  2006/2007 Rich Stabile
  2007/2008 Rich Stabile
  2008/2009 Rich Stabile
  2009/2010 Rich Stabile
  2010/2011 Jan Maria Jagush
  2011/2012 Jan Maria Jagush
  - General
    - Alumni Directory 1994, 1999, 2003 (Box 1.5)
    - Alumni Hall, Dedication, 1997 (Box OS 1)
    - Ancell Alumni, 1981-1982, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bank Books, 1929-1957 (Box OS 2)
    - Bulletin, Danbury State Normal School, April 1 - November 1, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bylaws and Constitution (ca. 1941-1942), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Financial Reports, 1932-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Homecoming Program, 1960-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Invitation, 1934, 2000, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Financial Ledgers, 1961-1966 (Box OS 2)
    - Financial Ledgers, 1967-1972 (Box OS 2)
    - Minutes & Clippings, 1921-1944 (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
    - Minutes, 1957-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters: Alumni News, 1953-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
    - Newsletters: Alumni News, 1967-2002 (Box OS 1)
    - Newsletters: Alumni News, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters: Alumni News, 2002-2010 (Box 1, Folder 26-32)
    - Newsletters: Call Letter, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters: Journal of the Western Alumni Association, 1988-1995 (Box OS 1)
    - Newsletters: Alumni Newsletter, 1942-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17-20A)
      Folder 17, "Dear Alumnus", 1942 lists alums and the branch of service in which they were serving; includes names of women serving in the WAVEs and WAACs. Subsequent issues discuss status of alums and students in the service during World War II.
    - Newsletters: Western Alumnus, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1988-2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Newsletters: Western Alumnus, 1978-1981 (Box OS 1)
    - Reunion, Class of 1951, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Reunion, Class of 1964 and 1969, 1964, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Reunion, Class of 1942, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Reunion, Class of 1911 (scrapbook), 1932 (Box OS 2)
    - Athletic Hall of Fame, 1997; RG7_1_37_x (Box 1, Folder 33)
      2009 Accretion
    - Athletic Hall of Fame, 2001; RG7_1_38_x (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Athletic Hall of Fame, Programs, 2001-2002; RG7_1_39_x (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Athletic Hall of Fame, Correspondence, 2002; RG7_1_40_x (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Athletic Hall of Fame (programs), 2003-2004; RG7_1_41_x (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Athletic Hall of Fame (invitations), 2004; RG7_1_42_x (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Athletics, Media Guides, 1996-1998; RG7_1_43_x (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Athletics, Media Guides, 1999-2001; RG7_1_44_x (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Athletics, Media Guides, 2002-2003; RG7_1_45_x (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Athletics, Media Guides, 2004-2005; RG7_1_46_x (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Athletics, NCAA Div III Womens Basketball Final Four championship, 2000; RG7_1_47_x (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Athletics, Sports Schedules, 1996-1997; RG7_1_48_x (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Newsletters, Correspondence, 1986-1987; RG7_1_49_x (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - By-Laws, 1978-1986; RG7_1.1_1_x (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
    - By-Law Revision Committee Minutes, 1992-1993; RG7_1.1_2_x (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
    - By-Laws and Amendment, 1993-1994; RG7_1.1_3_x (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
    - Commencement Work Papers, 1975; RG7_1.1_4_x (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
    - Commencement Work Papers, 1976; RG7_1.1_5_x (Box 1.1, Folder 5)
    - Commencement Work Papers, 1978; RG7_1.1_6_x (Box 1.1, Folder 6)
    - Luncheons (Annual)Programs and Survey, 1985-1992; RG7_1.1_7_x (Box 1.1, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of Danbury Normal School Alumnae Association Meeting, 1932-1936; RG7_1.1_8_x (Box 1.1, Folder 8)
    - Minutes of Danbury State Teachers College Alumni Assn., 1937-1941; RG7_1.1_9-14_x (Box 1.1, Folder 9-14)
    - Minutes of Danbury State Teachers College Alumni Assn., 1962-1971; RG7_1.2_1_x (Box 1.2, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of Western Connecticut State University Alumni Assocation, 1996-1998; RG7_1.2_2-4_x (Box 1.2, Folder 2-4)
    - Westside Classroom Building (clippings and photos), 1977-1982; RG7_1.2_5_x (Box 1.2, Folder 5)
    - Memorabilia, Class of 1939 (Locust Ave. School Register, DeeTeeCee) donated by Ruth Pester Wilson), 1937-1939; RG7_1.2_6-8_x (Box 1.2, Folder 6-8)
    - Memorabilia, Class of 1951, includes photographs of Do-Day, Curly Hall, student/faculty baseball game, tennis court, Education Conference in NYC), donated by Neil Wagner 11/1/01, 1947-1976; RG7_1.2_9-10_x (Box 1.2, Folder 9-10)
    - Memorabilia, Class of 1934, donated by Irene C. Gorman., 1932-1934 (Box 1.2, Folder 11)
      1934 Commencement and photograph of 1934 Business Education Class taken in 1932
    - Curley Hall Dedication, March 13, 1949 (Box 1.2, Folder 12)
    - Kraus, Helen A., class of 1927, Rambles, Brambles & Stardust, 2001 (Box 1.2, Folder 13)
    - Class of 1998 banner celebrating 100th graduation (Item 18)
      2009 Accretion (location: top bay 9)
    - WXCI - 25th Anniversary (History, Alumni, clippings), 1973-1998; RG7_1.3_1-6_x (Box 1.3, Folder 1-6)
    - Reunions, DSC Classes of 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944 & 1945, 2003 (Box 1.3, Folder 7)
      2009 accretion
    - Reunion, DSTC Class of December 13, 1945, 50th Reunion Luncheon, November 9, 1996 (Box 1.3, Folder 8)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1948, 50th Reunion Luncheon, 1998 (Box 1.3, Folder 9)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1949, 49th Reunion Luncheon, 1998 (Box 1.3, Folder 10)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1950, 2000 (Box 1.3, Folder 11)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1951 (video tape), 2002 (Box 1.3, Folder 12)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1952, 2002 (Box 1.3, Folder 12.1)
    - Reunions, DSTC Class of 1954, 50th Reunion Phaquioque, August 29, 2004 (Box 1.3, Folder 13)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1959 - 41st, 45th Reunion, 2000, 2004 (Box 1.3, Folder 14)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1960, September 23, 2000 (Box 1.4, Folder 1)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1961, September 15-16, 2001 (invitation only) (Box 1.4, Folder 2)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1962, 40th Class Reunion, October 26, 2002 (Box 1.4, Folder 3)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1963, 40th Anniversary, October 18, 2003 (Box 1.4, Folder 4)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1964, April 28, 1990 (Box 1.4, Folder 5)
    - Reunions, DSC Class of 1964, 40th Class Reunion, October 2004 (Box 1.4, Folder 6)
    - Reunions, WCSC Class of '68, '69, & '70, November 6, 1999 (Box 1.4, Folder 7)
    - Reunions, WCSC Class of 1975, October 14, 2000 (Box 1.4, Folder 8)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, October 16, 1998 (Box 1.4, Folder 9)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, October 8, 1999 (Box 1.4, Folder 10)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, October 13, 2000 (Box 1.4, Folder 11)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, October 4, 2002 (Box 1.4, Folder 12)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, October 3, 2003 (Box 1.4, Folder 13)
    - Reunions, Golden Circle Luncheon, 2005 (Box 1.4, Folder 14)
    - Reunions, WCSU Music Department Reunion, Classes 1954-1963, 1999 (Box 1.4, Folder 15)
    - Addresses (duplicates), Mar 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
      General
      2012 accretion
    - Alumni Board Members, Minutes of Board of Directors Meetings and Annual Business Meeting, and By-Laws, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
      2012 accretion Applications, Board of Directors prior to August 1995 Applications, Board of Directors prior to August 1995
    - Applications, Board of Directors prior to August 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Commencement (VHS), Dec 3,, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Committees, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Financials, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Minutes and Agendas, Board of Directors Meetings, Committees, By-Laws, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13-17)
    - Miscellaneous (handwritten minutes, invoices), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18-22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Phone-a-thon, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Phone Lists, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Proposals, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Reports, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
    - State of the University, 1992-1996, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Proposal for Building Development and Site Acquisitions at WCSU, ca 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Basketball Tournament, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Golf Registration Report and Pictures (CD), April 17, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Events (Includes Committees, Homecoming, banquets, etc.), 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Reunion Gala, Classes of 1957, 1962, 1967, 1972, 1977, 1982, 1987, 1992 and 1997, Oct 6, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Reunion, Nursing, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 35-36)
    - Reunion, WXCI Guest Book, Dec 18, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Science Building Ribbon Cutting Invitation, Sept 26, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - WCSU Alumni Association mugs (2); pewter apple, DTC Class of '52; WCSC Class of 1971 glass donated by Peter Serniak; WCSU Alumni Association pewter dish; WCSU Alumni Association "Welcome Class of 1960" photo holder key fob; WCSU Alumni Association pin; The Mark Twain House glass paperweight; "Great Seal of the United States of America" commemorative coin; "Great Seal of the United States of America" commemorative coin, 1995-2005 (Box 12)
  - Photographs
    - Buildings and Grounds
      - Alumni Hall: Dedication, candids and posed, 1997 (Box 1.6, Folder 1Alumni Hall: Renovation (indoor/outdoor))
        30 4x6 color
      - Alumni Hall: Renovation (indoor/outdoor), 1998 (Box 1.6, Folder 2)
        Six 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Alumni Clock: Outdoor, 2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 3)
        Three 4x6 color Construction: Outdoor, Haas Library, Old Main, Fairfield Hall, Alumni Hall
      - Construction: Outdoor, Haas Library, Old Main, Fairfield Hall, Alumni Hall, 1999-2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 4)
        14 4x6 color
      - Fairfield Hall: Exterior, ca.1930 (Box 1.6, Folder 5)
        One 3x4.5 b/w Old Main: Indoor, miscellaneous Old Main: Indoor, miscellaneous
      - Old Main: Indoor, miscellaneous, ca.2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 6)
        Eight 4x6 color
      - Warner Hall: Dedication, candids/posed, 2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 7)
        50 5x6 color w/contact sheet
      - O'Neill Athletic & Convocation Center/Feldman Arena: Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1995 (Box 1.6, Folder 8)
        Eight 5x7 color Alumni Images: 1957 Alums at Mac's Halfway Restaurant (labeled)
    - Events
      - Alumni Images: 1957 Alums at Mac's Halfway Restaurant (labeled), 1996 (Box 1.6, Folder 9)
        One 3.5x4.5 color
      - Alumni Images: 1957 Alums at Mac's Halfway Restaurant (labeled), 1997 (Box 1.6, Folder 10)
      - Alumni Images: 1957 Alums at TK's Café, Danbury (labeled), 1999 (Box 1.6, Folder 11)
      - Alumni Images: Donna Balbierer, posed, 1997 (Box 1.6, Folder 12)
        One 4x6 color
      - Alumni Images: David L. Holmes, Class of 1970, ca.1995 (Box 1.6, Folder 13)
        One 4x5 b/w
      - Alumni Images: Mort Johnson, Class of 1942, ca.2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 14)
      - Alumni Images: Ed McGivern, Class of 1949, 1999 (Box 1.6, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Images: Beth McNamara, Class of 1928 (Includes daughter Mary Warlop, and Simone & Frank McNamara, son), 1999 (Box 1.6, Folder 16)
        Two 3.5x4 color
      - Alumni Images: Clarice Osiecki, Class of 1988, ca.2000 (Box 1.6, Folder 17)
        One 4x6 Color
      - Alumni Images: Betty Ann (Ritch) "48 and Richard Smith, 1998 (Box 1.6, Folder 18)
      - The Big "E" (Eastern States Exposition): CSUS Booth with staff, candids (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.6, Folder 19)
        19 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll A, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 20)
        13 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll B, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 21)
        26 4x6 color Centennial: 5K Run, Roll C
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll C, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 22)
        24 4x6 color Centennial: 5K Run, Roll D
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll D, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 23)
        34 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll E, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 24)
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll F, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 25)
        24 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll G, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 26)
        33 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll H, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 27)
        37 4x6 color
      - Centennial: 5K Run, Roll I, 2003 (Box 1.6, Folder 28)
      - Child Care Center: Grand Opening, candids (Includes Dr. Roach,Mayor Eriquez), 1997 (Box 1.7, Folder 1)
        35 4x6 color
      - Commencement: Breakfast, posed and candids (unlabeled), 1994 (Box 1.7, Folder 2)
        11 4x6 color
      - Commencement: Outdoor, candids (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 3)
        Five 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Commencement: Outdoor, posed (Helen Margaret Gereg), 1959 (Box 1.7, Folder 4)
        One 8x10 color
      - Connecticut Society of CPA's Educational Trust Fund Grant: Group, posed, Accounting Society and Accounting Department (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 5)
        One 5x7 b/w
      - Dinner Theater: Meet Me In St. Louis (dinner images), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 6)
        26 4x6 color
      - Dinner Theater: Meet Me In St. Louis (dinner images), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 6)
      - Do-Day: Class of 1953 Deans (Janet Brudis, Dean of Men, and Beaver Butera, Dean of Women) (Box 1.7, Folder 7)
        One 8.5x11 b/w
      - Golf Classic: Candids and posed (unlabeled), 1998 (Box 1.7, Folder 8)
        31 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Golf Classic: Candids and posed (labeled/unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.7, Folder 9)
        22 4x6 color w/contact sheet and negatives
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Posed (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.7, Folder 10)
        16 4x6 color
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Candids and posed, (unlabeled), 1998 (Box 1.7, Folder 11)
        29 4x6 color
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Posed, scanned images (labeled), 1998 (Box 1.7, Folder 12)
        Five 4x6 color
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Candids and posed, Class of 1924,1929,1939,1940,1942 (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.7, Folder 13)
        24 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Candids and posed, Class of 1943,1946,1948,1949 (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.7, Folder 14)
        22 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Group, posed, Class of 1941, 1942, 1943 (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.7, Folder 15)
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Posed and candids, Classes of 1940,1941,1942 (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 16)
        25 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Posed and candids (unlabeled), 2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 17)
        17 4x6 color
      - Golden Circle Luncheon: Posed and candids (unlabeled), 2002 (Box 1.7, Folder 18)
        36 4x6 color
      - Masterson, Helen: Candids and posed, ca.1995 (Box 1.7, Folder 19)
      - O'Neill Center: Faculty and staff, candids (unlabeled), ca.2000 (Box 1.7, Folder 20)
      - Picnic: Faculty and staff, candids (inlcudes Pres. J. Roach and Denise Hogan), 1994 (Box 1.8, Folder 1)
      - Picnic: Class of 1940, 1941, 1942 at Sarah Sanford Park, Bridgewater, 2001 (Box 1.8, Folder 2)
        One 4x10.5 color
      - Regional Reception: North Carolina, candids and posed (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.8, Folder 3)
      - Regional Reception: Orlando, candids (unlabeled), 1999 (Box 1.8, Folder 4)
      - Reunion: Class of 1946 (unlabeled), 1996 (Box 1.8, Folder 5)
        Two 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Reunion: Class of 1947, 50th Reunion (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.8, Folder 6)
      - Reunion: Class of 1947, Women's Baseball Team (unlabeled), 1997 (Box 1.8, Folder 7)
      - Reunion: Class of 1948 and 1949 (Scanned Alumni News 12/98), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 8)
        Two 4x6 and four 5x7 color w/negatives
      - Reunion: Class of 1952, candids and posed (unlabeled), 1998 (Box 1.8, Folder 8)
        12 4x6 color w/negatives Reunion: Class of 1953, candids and posed (unlabeled)
      - Reunion: Class of 1953, candids and posed (unlabeled), 1995 (Box 1.8, Folder 10)